<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">tathva</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="sunburn_details">Soul. Turf. Corroboree. Friends. Food. Fun. Gargantuan Crowds. An exhilarating arena format. World music hits. A distinctively internationalist sensibility. It turns out all of them convene at the NITC Campus on the 19th of October for a night of reggae, jazz and punk. Sunburn is India’s premier music brand hosting some of the best festivals in the country. Ever since its inception, the premier festival has managed to rope in world music connoisseurs, melomanes and fanatics from across the globe. Tathva brings you exciting events, exhilarating proshows and more in a single, explosive package. The event is all set to take place at the OAT, the holy ground of musical inspiration and where DJ Clement and his team unleash all their spinning know-how.</string>
    <string name="the_down_troddence_details">\'The Down Troddence\', popularly known as \'TDT\' is a six piece Folk - Thrash Metal Band, originally from Kannur district in Kerala, India. The band currently consists of Munz (Vocals), Varun Raj (Guitar), Nezer Ahemed (Bass Guitar, Backing Vocals), Sushin Shyam (Keyboards, Backing Vocals), Ganesh Radhakrishnan (Drums), and Advaith Mohan (Guitar). The band has just finished recording their debut album, which is expected to be released by end of October 2013. TDT has seen enormous success in the Indian metal scene following the release of their first music video for the song \‘Shiva\’.</string>
    <string name="rock_band_details">All The Fat Children, a Bengaluru based rock band plays “Fat Rock”, a fitting genre they coined themselves, encompassing the diversity reflected in its three rejuvenating performers. Captivating the hearts of the audience, this group of exhilarating musicians ace the competition wherever they go and have headlined many shows and corporate events. With uniqueness as their signature, these young talents promote original music through their compositions like “My Favourite Heartbreaker”, “Crazy Girlfriend”, “November Forever”, “Somebody Else” and “ El Shaddai”.</string>
    <string name="southern_combo_details">KRISH:First Indian ever to work for Walt Disney on the New York Broadway Musicals, he made his mark internationally by playing the lead role in a Walt Disney Production. Since his debut song “Manjal Veyyil” (Vettayadu Vilayadu) , he has climbed the heights of fame through subsequent runaway successes like “June Ponal” (Unnale Unnale) , “Oru Mughamo”(Bheema) and "Adiye Kolluthe" (Vaaranam Aayiram). With several prestigious awards to his credit, this young and versatile singer has been tagged as the best performer of South India. This year, the Tathva stage is all set to catapult you into an exuberant nite that will leave you craving for more!\nRITA:Young and exceptionally talented, this singer has awed the South Indian film industry with her exhilarating list of block buster hits like “Vaada Mappilai” (Villu), ”Allegra”( Kanthasami), “Chandamama”(Rock and Roll) and “Aarane”(Urumi).Having worked with all leading music directors across the South Indian Film Industry with over 150 songs to her credit, this spirited on-stage performer likes to experiment with western and fusion styles. With this sizzling artist blazing on stage , revel in the heights of ecstasy and delve into the aura of her enchantment!</string>
    <string name="app_id">279143188956828</string>
    
    
</resources>
